slotpartners.com 2014-11-29

# Slotpartners :: Privacy Policy

### SlotPartners Privacy Policy

#### Your Personal Information

SlotPartners is concerned to protect the privacy of any personal information that you may choose to provide to us ("Personal Information"). Personal Information is any information about you and may include your name and address, date of birth, payment card details and any other information you may wish to provide. We will attempt to ensure that our use of your Personal Information is compliant with data protection and privacy regulations in the countries where we operate. Accordingly, we issue this Policy to inform you of our use of your Personal Information.

#### Is your Personal Information collected by our Websites?

If you provide your name and address on the public area of our Websites ([http://www.slotpartners.com](http://www.slotpartners.com/), [http://www.vippowerlounge.com](http://www.vippowerlounge.com/), [http://www.powerjackpot.com](http://www.powerjackpot.com/), [http://www.nedbet.com](http://www.nedbet.com/), [http://www.classicjackpot.com](http://www.classicjackpot.com/), [http://www.powerloungecasino.com](http://www.powerloungecasino.com/), [http://www.powerjackpotcasino.com](http://www.powerjackpotcasino.com/), ) in order to request information about our products and services, you may voluntarily provide additional Personal Information. You will be asked to provide your Personal Information in this area for the purposes of registering and opening an account with us.

If you are already our customer and have opened an account with us, you must use a password to enter the Websites or the Software. A "session cookie" may be used to enable you to leave and re-enter our Website without re-entering your password. Our web servers will record the webpages that you visit.

An IP address is a number that uniquely identifies your computer on the Internet. We may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, security, troubleshooting, and compiling aggregate information (such as how many visitors logged on to the Websites). When you visit a particular webpage, our servers may log your IP address.

#### How will we use your Personal Information

We will process your Personal Information in accordance with applicable data protection law. SlotPartners proposes to process your Personal Information for the following purposes: administering your account; maintaining our own accounts and records; monitoring websites usage levels and quality of service; and informing you about products and services that you may be interested in from time to time (the "Purposes"). Any recordings remain the property of SlotPartners and will be used only for the purposes above.

To ensure a good quality of service we may monitor any communication you have with us whether in writing or by electronic mail (the "Recordings").

#### Disclosing your Personal Information

Your Personal Information may, for the Purposes described above, be transferred or disclosed by us to any associated company or business partner which is well placed to process your Personal Information (the "Site Group") for the Purposes. We and these companies may from time to time retain third parties to process your Personal Information for the Purposes and such processing will be governed by a contract in the form required by law. Where required by law or regulation your personal data may also be disclosed to an applicable governmental, regulatory or enforcement authority.

SlotPartners will take reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to protect your Personal Information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure.

The Websites operated by SlotPartners may contain links to third-party websites. When you follow these links you leave SlotPartners and are transferred to a third-party website. You should be aware that these third-party websites may have their own information collection practices and privacy policies. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties that have websites linked to SlotPartners. If you follow a third-party advertisement or link, the privacy policies of the third-party website that you link to will govern the use of your information by that website’s operator. The Privacy Policy does not extend to these external websites. Please refer directly to the privacy policies on such third-party websites. We assume no responsibility or liability for the actions of such third parties with respect to their use of your information or otherwise. Accordingly, please make sure you are aware of and comfortable with the privacy policies of any third-party websites to which you are transferred by following a link.

In the event of a merger or consolidation of SlotPartners, or the sale of all or substantially all of its stock or assets, or the transfer of the operation and distribution of certain products or Services to a third-party, or bankruptcy, your personal information may be transferred to SlotPartners's successor or assign resulting from such events.

#### No Absolute Safeguards

Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorised third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control.

#### Your Role in Protecting Your Privacy

Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any account /username /ID or password, and you should always be careful and responsible whenever disclosing information online.

#### Consent

By providing your Personal Information and registering with us or logging on with us when you enter the Websites, you freely consent to the Site Group processing and disclosing your Personal Information for the Purposes and otherwise in the manner set out in this Policy. If you wish to qualify, vary, modify or limit your consent in any way then please notify us by using the Contact page of our Websites.
